top10answers.com 2013-06-09

# About Top10answers.com Privacy

| 

Untitled Document

## Privacy Policy for Top10answers.com

Top10answers.com is owned and operated by IAC Search & Media, a wholly owned business of IAC, which operates several dozen brands such as Chemistry.com, Citysearch, CollegeHumor, Dictionary.com, Evite, GarageGames, Gifts.com, Match.com, Pronto, ServiceMagic, Shoebuy, and Vimeo. For a list of all of IAC's businesses, please visit [www.iac.com](http://www.iac.com/).

We respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We provide this Privacy Policy so that our users (“ **you** ”) will know what information is being collected about you and your activities on Top10answers.com, (the “ **Site** ”) how that information is being used, and with whom it is being shared. This Privacy Policy describes the online privacy practices applicable to the web ( the “ **Site** ”) and the various services (“ **Services** ”) we provide on or through the Site. 

By using the Site and Services, you are agreeing to the collection and use of certain information about you in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

We update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes in the ways we may collect, use, or share information, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes on the Site. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to become and remain familiar with it. The Privacy Policy includes at the top of the first page the date of the most recent change. 

This Privacy Policy addresses the following issues: 

What types of information do we collect?

How may we use the information we collect?

How are cookies used on the Site?

What information may we share with third parties?

What happens when you leave the Site to go to other Internet sites?

What is our policy regarding personally identifiable information from children under 13?

Do we take security precautions to protect your information?

Are there special considerations if you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States?

Whom can you ask if you have privacy-related questions?

### What types of information do we collect?

Each time you visit the Site, we collect the limited information that your browser makes available whenever you visit any website. This information includes: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform); (d) your browser language; and (e) the data in any undeleted "cookies" that your browser previously accepted from us (see "How are cookies used on the Site?" below). Additionally, when you enter a search query using the Site or Services, we will receive the query text and process it, together with the above data, to return a search results page to you. If you have modified your browser settings so that address-bar search queries and erroneous domain name system (DNS) requests are submitted to us, we may also receive any search query or misspelled URL that you enter into your browser's address bar. 

Beginning with search queries received on or before July 1, 2009, we disassociate your query text data from your IP address and your unique cookie ID (see "How are cookies used on the Sites?" below) after a period of 18 months, except in limited circumstances, such as requests to retain the information by law enforcement.

The Site and Services usually do not require registration or submission of an account name or email address in order to use them. However, you would provide to us your email address if you submitted a help request to us via email. The amount of information that you choose to disclose to us is completely up to you.

### How may we use the information we collect?

We use the information that we collect to improve the overall quality of your experience with the Site and Services, and to facilitate evaluation, improvement, and development of the Services. We aggregate query information for internal reporting purposes and optimization of advertising revenue. We count, track, and aggregate our visitors' activities in our analysis of general traffic flows at the Site (e.g., tracking where users come from, what pages they select within the Site, how they interact with search results, etc.). 

Information about the search queries you submit to the Sites and how you interact with search results may also be used to personalize the content and advertisements that we present to you. We may, based on the search queries you submit and the search results you select (including paid search results), draw inferences about your interests and display advertisements matched to such interests. You may receive such customized ads on the Site and on third-party sites (see also "What information do we share with third parties?" below). If you would like to terminate our access to your search history you may remove our cookies from your computer (see "How are cookies used on the Sites?" below and consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies).

If you choose to submit your name, email address, or other information, we may use such information to contact you to respond to a request from you, or in connection with legal proceedings, or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. We do not associate your search queries or selected search results in any manner with your name, email address, or other information, unless required to do so by legal process.

### How are cookies used on the Sites?

Our use of cookies on the Sites. We use cookies and other technology such pixel tags to track traffic flow and patterns of travel within and among the Site. Cookies are a standard Internet technology that allows us to store and retrieve information on a user's system. Our web server automatically asks a new user's browser whether it will accept our cookie file. If the user's browser accepts our cookie, our web server will record the cookie's unique ID for our use in internal reporting and for customized advertising (see "How do we use the information that we collect?" above). All of your search queries and interactions with search results on the Sites are associated with your unique cookie ID. When you use the Site we may use your cookie data to customize the Services and advertisements delivered to you (see "What information do we share with third parties?" below). 

Our cookies expire after two years, and all information from expired cookies is automatically deleted from our servers. If you would like to remove our cookies from your computer, you can delete them using your browser (consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies). If you choose to decline or remove cookies, please note that this may affect the quality of the Services.

We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way, or associate your name, email address, or personal information with your cookie data. We do not disclose cookie information to third parties, except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy (see "What information do we share with third parties?" below). 

_Use of cookies on our Site by third parties_. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site in order to present advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements on the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Sites. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad-serving company might collect from you. These companies have their own recordkeeping and data-retention policies. If you would like to consider your options for limiting use of such information by advertising companies, or would like to learn more about this practice, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. We also use third party vendors to help us better understand our user demographics. These vendors may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Site to provide their services to us. 

### What information may we share with third parties?

We do not share your name name, or email address or any other personal information with third parties for the purpose of enabling them to send you information about their products or services (or for any other purpose, except to respond to legal process as described below). 

_Third-party service providers_. Some elements or features of the Sites, such as the sponsored results advertising on our search-results pages, are supplied to us by third parties under contract. We may supply some of the information we collect from you to those third parties so that they can provide those elements or features for display on the Site. We may share the following information with third parties: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform); (d) your browser language; (e) the data in any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us; and (f) the search queries you submit. For example, when you submit a query, we transmit it (and some of the related information described above) to our paid-listing providers in order to generate relevant advertising to display in response to your query and to optimize the number and quality of sponsored results that will be provided to you on the Site. We may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers. If you provide us with answers to voluntary survey questions, we may furnish this information to our advertisers and partners in the form of group statistics compiled from our users' answers to such questions.

_Law enforcement/legal requirements_. We may disclose any information you voluntarily submit to us, as well as any other information we have about you (such as your IP address, the search queries you have submitted, and the search results you have selected) in order to comply with court orders, subpoenas, or regulatory obligations, or when otherwise required to do so by law. We also may disclose such information in compliance with a law-enforcement or other governmental request, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service.

_Corporate restructuringi_. We also may transfer your information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets).

### What happens when you leave the Site to go to other Internet sites?

We do not control the information collection and dissemination policies of third-party companies. When you are on the Site, you may be directed to other site that are beyond our control. For example, if you click on a search result, the click may take you to a third-party website. These other site may independently collect data from or about you, solicit information from you, or place their own cookies on your computer. We are not responsible for any use of the information such third-party site may collect. 

### What is our policy regarding personally identifiable information from children under 13?

In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. Registration on the Site and for the Services is not available to anyone under the age of 13. 

### Do we take security precautions to protect your information?

We have security measures in place that are designed to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to information we collect online. We also seek to limit access to our users’ information to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their jobs. These employees have been informed of the need to maintain the security and confidentiality of such information. Unfortunately, no security system can be 100% secure; accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that we collect online.

### Are there special considerations if you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States?

If you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States, your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data-protection and other laws in the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your own country. Please be assured, however, that we seek to take reasonable steps to protect your privacy. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities and those third parties with whom we may share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Whom can you ask if you have privacy-related questions?

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed here.
